



#### Profile

## **Full Stack Developer**

Experienced full-stack developer, who has 4 years experience in developing websites. Excels at Ruby on Rails and Javascript. Possesses profound knowledge in web services and cloud-based services. Exhibits strong self-taught skills, excellent team-working and communication skills. Core competencies includes:

Web Development - Ruby on Rails - HTML5/CSS3 - Javascript - RESTful API Design - Responsive Design - Continuous Integration.

## Experience

Oct 2015 - present

## Research Assistant, CCIS Department, Aalto University

Research into Internet of Things topic.

Skills gained: Research Skills, Self Motivated, Presentation Skills

#### Sep 2013 — Aug 2015

### Senior Web Developer, VCCloud Department, VC Corp

- Developing 1 dashboard, 2 web-based back office tools and numerous RESTful web services for VCCloud's Cloud Computing System, being involved in both back-end and front-end development.
- Deploying and maintaining VCCloud's web servers.

Skills gained: Ruby on Rails, RESTful API Design, Documentation, Deployment, CI

# Mar 2013- Jul 2014

**Research Assistant**, International Institute for Computational Science and Engineering, Hanoi University of Science and Technology

- Working in a research project on Cloud Computing technologies, implemented a cloud computing system in 6 months.
- Designing, developing, deploying and maintaining 3 web application services for cloud computing system BKCloud.

Skills gained: Ruby on Rails, Cloud Computing, Web-based Service Architecture

#### Jul 2012 - Jul 2013

#### Web Developer, Framgia, Inc.

■ Developing websites using RoR, MySQL, PostgreSQL, HTML5 / CSS3, JavaScript.

Skills gained: Ruby on Rails, Web Development, UI/UX, Independent Working

#### Education

# 2015 - Present

#### Master in Computer Science, Aalto University, Finland

- Majoring in Web Technologies and Applications
- Honours Programme Participant.

#### 2009 - 2014

# **Engineer in Information Technology,** Hanoi University of Science and Technology, Vietnam

- Major in Information Technology.
- Very Good Degree.
- GPA: 8.76/10 1st rank in ICT programme cohort 54

Language Skills

Mother tongue(s)

Vietnamese

Other language(s)

English — Proficient User

Technical Skills

	Years Experience	Skill Level
Languages		
Ruby	4	Advanced
HTML5/CSS3	4	Advanced
Javascript	4	Advanced
Python	2	Intermediate
Frameworks		
Ruby/Rails	4	Advanced
Javascript/Jquery	4	Advanced
Javascript/AngularJS	2	Intermediate
PHP/WordPress	2	Novice
Databases		
MySQL	4	Advanced
PostgresSQL	4	Advanced
MongoDB	2	Intermediate
Redis	2	Intermediate